Guide to the Arthur Kopit Papers MSS.141
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Projects
  - Animal Hospital, 1986; 31142040619218 (Box 1)
    "Steven May--Pet Limo Interview"
    Two sketchbooks moved to Flat Box 1
    Offsite Barcode: 31142040619218
  - The Bell Witch Variations by Betty D. Matarese, May 27, 1987, 31142040619226 (Box 2)
    Script and scene fragments, handwritten notes, production notes, memos; pamphlets, articles, and other research material on small Tennessee towns and the legend of the Bell Witch, audition applications and head shots, administrative materials relating to Kopit's position in Tennessee, "Vanderbilt Review" Spring 1986, Austin Peay State University Directory, index cards; 4 small notebooks, all only partially filled.
    Publications
    Tennessee Trivia Compiled by Ernie and Jill Couch, Rutledge Hill Press, Nashville.1985
    The Tennessee Sampler by Peter Jenkins and Friends, Thomas Nelson Publishers, Nashville. 1985
    Zone 3 Spring 1986, poetry journal of Austin Peay State University
    The Bell Witch of Tennessee by Charles Bailey Bell, Harriet Parks Miller, Published by Charles Elder, Nashville. Original edition 1934, facsimile edition 1972.
    Authenticated History of the Bell Witch and Other Stories of the World's Greatest Unexplained Phenomenon by M.V. Ingram, Rare Book Reprints, Nashville. Original edition 1894, facsimile edition 1961.
    Audio Cassettes
    "The Bells of Adams 1 and 2"
    "The Bells of Adams Sides 3 and 4"
    Offsite Barcode: 31142040619226
  - Between the Wars, 1991-1992; 31142040619234 (Box 3)
    Work (in one instance titled "The Testing Ground") on an unproduced screenplay based on a stage play by Ellen Kesend ("To Have and To Hold") about the Spanish Civil War and Robert Capa. Notebooks, news articles, research, screenplay drafts.
    "Spanish Civil War thoughts (pre-meeting)"
    "Spanish Civil War phone call with Disney 4/29/92"
    "2nd Disney Meeting in L.A. (I did not record the first)"
    "Some of my comments re: Disney notes"
    "Between the Wars Tape no. 1 3/5/1992" 1 micro cassette in env.
    "Sp. Civil War tape no. 2 3/16/92" 1 micro cassette in env.
    Note: One folder oversized material at end of box.
    One sketchbook has extensive post-it note annotation.
    Extensive historical news clippings that might be indexed and discarded.
    Need on audio tape case
    Offsite Barcode: 31142040619234
  - Note: Once the oversized materials in this box have been stored separately, the remaining folders can be fit into Box 2, hence the box designation 2a, 1997; 31142040619242 (Box 4)
    Blindsight
    Plot summary, research materials, correspondence
    "Marianne May '98" (miniature cassette)
    "Arthur to Marianne, 10/24/97"
    "Marianne Shennefield, Oct. 6th" 3 tapes
    "Marianne, Oct 24th"
    "Alexi on Marianne"
    "Dick Russell Talks About Marianne Shennefield"
    "Dick Russell, May 14, 1998
    "Marianne"
    Video Cassettes
    "Marianne", VHS, T-120
    Computer Media
    unlabeled 3 1/2" diskette
    Need case for audio tape and diskette
    Offsite Barcode: 31142040619242
  - Blue Angel Box 1, 1992-1994; 31142040619259 (Box 5)
    Contracts, receipts, other documents with HBO for work; index cards, sketches and notes; typescript "very rough first draft" 4/25/93; first Draft 5/21/93; 3 bound notebooks, sketchbooks including disbound signatures
    "'Blue Angel' Notes on opening. If Stuck, listen!" 1 micro cassette
    "Spoto Interview, NY, 9/16/92" 2 tapes
    "Spoto second visit, 10/8/1992"
    "Spoto 3rd Interview 10/21/1992" 2 tapes and two back up tapes
    "Interview with Burt Bacharach re: Marlene, 7/19/93" 1 tape and 1 backup
    "Burt Bacharach 1st meeting my remarks"
    "Blue Angel HBO notes tape #1 Sue Pollacs(?), Laurette Hayden
    "Blue Angel HBO notes tape #2
    "Ella on Dietrich in Berlin"
    "Donald Spoto"
    Unlabeled tape
    Offsite Barcode: 31142040619259
  - Blue Angel Box 2, 1992-1994; 31142040619267 (Box 6)
    Publications most heavily annotated
    Maria Riva, Marlene Dietrich (Bloomsbury: London; Alfred A. Knopf: New York, 1992)
    Donald Spoto, Blue Angel: The Life of Marlene Dietrich (Doubleday: New York, 1992) 2 copies
    Steven Bach, Marlene Dietrich: Life and Legend (William Morrow and Company: 1992)
    Marlene Dietrich, Marlene (Grove Press: New York, 1989)
    Donald Spoto, Lenya: A Life (Ballantine Books: New York, 1990)
    Note: Books heavily marked with annotated post-it notes
    Offsite Barcode: 31142040619267
  - Cheeky Peeky, 1995-1996; 31142040619275 (Box 7)
    Note: All folder titles reflect original labels of hanging files these records were stored in. Cassettes scattered throughout box. One empty folder labeled "outline and notes"
    Script, notes, articles and research, correspondence, especially between coauthors.
    "Cheeky Peeky" micro cassette
    "Arthur's Notes--Cheeky Peeky"
    "Phone interview with Sam Cohen 'father of the neutron bomb' on 'Red Mercury'"
    "Cheeky Peeky Jan '96 (Alex's Comments)"
    "Sergei, Alex, Arthur 11/18/95" 2 tapes
    "Conference Call 6/27/96, Arthur, Zach, Douglas Reuther, Nana Greenwald, Brian Alexander" 2 tapes
    Alex on Cheeky Peeky"
    3 1/2" Diskette, "Cheeky Peeky"
    5" floppy diskette "ASCII (DOS) Kopit 2; Lois Porro Transcription"
    Publications Stephen Handelman,
    Comrade Criminal: Russia's New Mafiya (Yale University Press: New Haven, Conn., 1995)
    Offsite Barcode: 31142040619275
  - Deception Box 1, 1988; 31142040619283 (Box 8)
    Note: Titles on folders reflect titles of original folders.
    Index cards, notebooks, one large sketchbook, magazine and newspaper clippings, drafts, revisions with comments.
    Micro tape "Carole Hart: 2 phone calls re: 3rd draft of Deception Jan '88" Envelope says 3 tapes but only one present
    Peter Sheldon, ed. Fodor's Turkey 1987 (Fodor's Travel Guides: New York, 1986)
    Marilyn Jenkins, Manuel Keene, Islamic Jewelry in the Metropolitan Museum of Art (The Museum: New York, n.d.)
    Esin Atil, The Age of Sultan Suleyman the Magnificent (National Gallery of Art: Washington; Harry N. Abrams: New York, 1987)
    Note: In this box was found 6"-7" of drafts and index cards for "The Shroud". Material removed and placed with other Shroud materials.
    Note: Sketchbook and exhibition catalog moved to Flat Box 1.
    Offsite Barcode: 31142040619283
  - Deep Purple 1995, 31142040619309 (Box 9)
    Sketchbooks, photocopies of images
    VHS "Video of Deep Purple recording studio in Orlando"
    VHS "Deep Purple BBC Interviews"
    Compact Discs (published)
    Deep Purple, Deep Purple in Rock: Anniversary Edition c1995
    Deep Purple, Perfect Strangers c1994
    Deep Purple, Made in Japan c1973
    Deep Purple, Machine Head c1972
    Deep Purple, Who Do They Think They Are c1992
    Deep Purple, Nobody's Perfect c1988
    "'Bitchin'--Mystery Band"
    "Roger Glover---Tunes"
    "Trog---rock band fight"
    "Orlando-Tuesday evening, I talk with Rodger Glover"
    "Deep Purple's recording studio in Orlando"
    "DP--Orlando 2nd visit"
    Micro Audio Cassettes in labeled env.s
    "Orlando Wed night I talk with Roger Olner...Tape 1" 1 tape
    "Orlando (Sunday) My Comments and Reactions" 1 tape
    "Nina Play...." 1 tape
    "Tape 1 Orlando (9/1/95)...and Tape B 9/2/95" 2 tapes
    "Orlando Sat night DURING dinner" 1 tape
    "Sat morning, Rose Glover" 1 tape
    "Orlando Monday #1, 2, 3" 3 tapes
    "Sat night in Orlando (9/2) 3rd tape of the evening" 1 tape
    "Saturday, RG Montserrat!" 1 tape
    "Orlando 9/1/95, 9/2/95" 3 tapes
    "Tape 101 9/2/95" 1 tape
    "Orlando (Tuesday)" 5 tapes
    "Orlando Monday and Tuesday 2nd visit" 7 tapes
    Discovery of America
    Handwritten and typescript drafts, pamphlets, research material.
    Note: legal sized script pages and photo copies moved to Flat Box 2.
    Offsite Barcode: 31142040619309
  - Discovery of America, unknown; 31142040619317 (Box 10)
    Scripts, large amount of handwritten drafts, contracts. Includes folders of notes and thoughts for other possible works including The Woblns (tentative title).
    Photographs in last folder in box.
    Offsite Barcode: 31142040619317
  - Dream House, 1981-1991; 31142040619325 (Box 11)
    Notebooks, tapes, typescripts and handwritten drafts, news clippings, magazines, home supply catalogs, mail order house plans, brochures.
    "VHS "Security [20/20]
    Audio Cassettes (many in coin env.s scattered throughout box)
    "Oct. Current Dreamhouse" 2 microcassettes
    "Dream House microcassettes" 3 microcassettes
    "4/30/91 Tapes DreamHouse" 1 micro cassette, one empty container
    "Dream House 9/13/91 and 9/16/91 L.A. Mike Manheim" 4 microcassettes
    "5/13/91 Leslie's remarks on Dreamhouse" 1 micro cassette
    One loose empty case
    "TDK tape about treehouse (side A) Dreamhouse current tapes 4/24/91 (side B 5/6/91)" 2 microcassettes
    "Computer voice in phone" 1 micro cassette loose not in env.
    "Dream House Rollins Interview by Dave Weintraub" 1 micro cassette
    "Side A...Jules and Bob" 1 micro cassette
    Offsite Barcode: 31142040619325
  - Dream House Box 2, 1991-1992; 31142040619333 (Box 12)
    Index cards, spiral notebooks, correspondence, news clippings, publications, research materials, typescript drafts
    Headquarters, Department of the Army, TM-31-200-1 Department of the Army Technical Manual Unconventional Warfare Devices and Techniques References (Headquarters, Department of the Army: Washington D.C., April 1966)
    Headquarters, Department of the Army, FM 5-31 Department of the Army Field Manual Boobytraps (Headquarters, Department of the Army: Washington D.C., September 1965)
    "total security #1" 1 micro cassette
    "Integrated Security System" 1 micro cassette
    "Dream House 3/91" 1 micro cassette
    "2 Tapes conversation with Russell and Erica re: the architect" 2 microcassettes in env.
    George Carlin, A Place for My Stuff (Atlantic Recording Corporation: New York, c1981)
    "Dream House Security Westinghouse #1 #3, Total Security, The Bug" 3 microcassettes in env.
    "Dream HOuse" 1 micro cassette in env.
    :Dream House Michael Wang Phone Conversation" 1 micro cassette in sealed white env.
    "Dreamhouse re: Melvin Douglas Figure" 1 micro cassette in env.
    "Rollins Security (Nov. 1990--re. NBC) Sat. Nov. 10" 1 micro cassette in env. with note
    "Dream House Interview 'New Canaan Security'" 1 micro cassette in env. with note
    "Security Solutions" Sat Nov. 10" 1 micro cassette in env. with note
    env. with empty tape case.
    Note: Sketch pads, pages and other materials moved to Flat Box 2.
    Offsite Barcode: 31142040619333
  - End of the World Box 1, 1983-1986; 31142040619341 (Box 13)
    Correspondence, photographs of productions, promotional materials, news clippings, contracts, programs and playbills, records and details of royalties, publication, scripts, script revisions.
    Note: stack of photos in folder 2 (with poster to be separated), 4, 5, 11, and second from last folder.
    New York Times Magazine moved to Flat Box 2.
    Offsite Barcode: 31142040619341
  - End of the World Box 2, 1984; 31142040619358 (Box 14)
    Scripts, many annotated or referring to specific productions, news clippings, research, notebooks, magazines, journals.
    Arthur Kopit, End of the World (Hill and Wang: New York, 1984)
    Stewart Steven. The Spymasters of Israel (Macmillan Publishing: New York, 1980)
    Congress of the United States, Office of Technology Assessment, The Effects of Nuclear War (May 1979)
    Amount of oversized material to be separated
    Offsite Barcode: 31142040619358
  - End of the World Box 3, 1984; 31142040619366 (Box 15)
    Research, correspondence, notes, drafts, extensive series of notes on small slips of paper and clippings inside labeled Manila envelopes, very early preparations for play.
    Ground Zero, Nuclear War: What's in it For You? (Pocket Books: New York, 1982)
    Two folders of sketch pages and notes moved to Flat Box 3.
    Offsite Barcode: 31142040619366
  - End of the World Box 4, 1984; 31142040619374 (Box 16)
    Diagrams, early notes, research, news clippings, scripts, drafts, newspapers, reviews, foreign playbills and translations, galleys for publication.
    Ground Zero, Hope: Facing the Music on Nuclear War and the 1984 Elections (Long Shadow Books: New York, 1983)
    Note: 3 folders of maps, magazines, and research moved to Flat Box 3.
    Significant quantity of newspapers and magazines that should probably be listed in a bibliography and discarded.
    Offsite Barcode: 31142040619374
  - Ghosts, 1982; 31142040619382 (Box 17)
    Scripts, correspondence, news articles
    Snatch
    Handwritten early draft, typescript.
    Offsite Barcode: 31142040619382
  - Good Friends: A Musical, 1982-1986; 31142040619390 (Box 18)
    Good Friends is an original two person musical by Gil Perlroth. After seeing it in Stanford, Kopit became involved in rewriting the book, possibly under the new title "My Place or yours." It is unknown how far this project was developed. This box contains 10 copies of various versions of the original script from 1982-1986, a rough draft by Kopit, correspondence and contracts.
    "My Place or Yours? A Musical (Demo) Kopit/Perlroth""
    "Background Music"
    "Good Friends Demo c1986 Perlroth"
    "Good Friends c1986 Gil Perlroth Demo tape 8 songs"
    Offsite Barcode: 31142040619390
  - Hands of a Stranger, 1985-1987; 31142040619408 (Box 19)
    Screenplays, drafts, notebooks, index cards, promotional materials, news clippings.
    Robert Daley, Hands of a Stranger (Simon and Schuster: New York, 1985) Advanced uncorrected proof with heavy annotations
    Note: One legal notebook moved to Flat Box 4.
    Offsite Barcode: 31142040619408
  - High Society, 1997; 31142040619416 (Box 20)
    Playbills, notebooks, sketchbooks, script fragments and revisions.
    "Why Don't We Try Staying Home?"
    "1) Why Don't We Try Staying Home? 2) Say it With Gin"
    "Babies, Crying and Giggling"
    "True Love"
    "Wild Wedding Bells"
    ""Ted Sperling Plays Piano"
    Note: Includes oversized sketchbook moved to Flat Box 4.
    One script copy contains extensive post-it tabs.
    One audio tape needs container.
    Offsite Barcode: 31142040619416
  - Indians Box 1, 1968-; 31142040619424 (Box 21)
    "Cody's Will" (early version of play), extensive type- and handwritten drafts and revisions ca. 1968-1969, notes, playbills of the American premier, handwritten scenes with edits, Swedish translation of 1969, galley proofs, contact sheets of photographs of London production, correspondence, reviews.
    Offsite Barcode: 31142040619424
  - Indians Box 2, 1968-1969; 31142040619614 (Box 22)
    Royalty records, reviews, programs, handwritten and typewritten scripts and script fragments, prompt book (London), promotional materials from film.
    Note: Color production photos in front of box.
    Offsite Barcode: 31142040619614
  - Indians Box 3, 1968-1976, 1994; 31142040619622 (Box 23)
    Research materials, articles on film, large amount of original newspaper reviews and articles, notebook, playbills.
    Mindcontrol
    Research materials.
    "Wendy/Arthur"
    Offsite Barcode: 31142040619622
  - Legacy of a Mother's Murder (In a Child's Name) Box 1, 1987-1989; 31142040619630 (Box 24)
    Project with Peter Maas for ABC miniseries. When it aired in 1991 Kopit's name was not credited and it had been renamed "In a Child's Name". Notebooks and handwritten notes, correspondence, story treatments, script drafts, transcripts of conversations with Maas, copies of court documents, audio tapes.
    Note: all recordings are microcassettes unless indicated with an asterisk.
    Loose:
    "My response to second interview with Ken Taylor"
    "Jack Venturi"
    "...Peter Mass stuff"
    *"Peter Maas #2 Friday Oct. 16"
    *"Peter Maas #1 Friday Oct. 16"
    In cardboard box:
    "12/29/87 P. Maas"
    "Peter Maas 2 tapes [at Highdale] Tuesday July 7" 3 tapes in env.
    "Third tape Sunday July 19th Staten Island trip..." 2 tapes in env.
    "2nd meeting" 1 tape in env.
    "Dec. 15th conversation with Janice Miller" 1 tape in env.
    "Al Benigno phone call 1/14/88"
    "12/24 Janice Miller phone call" 1 tape in env.
    "Al Benigno" 1 tape in env.
    "10/16 N.J. Janice Miller 2 tapes" 2 tapes in env.
    "NJ tape Oct 16th Paul Chaiet" 1 tape in env.
    In Manila env.:
    *"Paul Chaiet Oct. 16th New Jersey" 1 tape in env.
    *"Peter Maas 3rd meeting June 19th Tape #2" 1 tape in env.
    *"Peter Maas 3rd meeting June 19th Tape #1" 1 tape in env.
    *"Peter Maas 2nd meeting June 12th one tape" 1 tape in env.
    In plastic bag:
    "Sunday Night...Tom Taylor...#2A" 2 tapes in env.
    "Sat afternoon Oct 15, 1988...first interview...Taylors, Marion, Ind." 3 tapes in env.
    "Other tapes...#5" 3 tapes in env.
    *"For Lois Porro 'Peter Maas Tape'" 1 tape in env.
    "Taylors Sunday #2" 3 tapes in env.
    "Tuesday Oct 18th 1988...Taylors day four #4" 3 tapes in env.
    "Ken Taylor Wed." 2 tapes in env.
    "Ken Taylor Thursday..." 4 tapes in env.
    "Taylors day #3...#3" 3 tapes in env.
    In second plastic bag:
    "Transcribed" 2 tapes in env.
    "plane ride to Ft. Wayne...#6" 1 tape in env.
    The following tapes were in the plastic bag inside a large Manila envelope marked "Peter Maas stuff to be transcribed":
    *Peter Maas, Dan Wigutow(?), ALK" 2 tapes in env.
    "Peter Maas/Dan Wigutow" 1 tape in env.
    "Visit to Celeste and Jeff's House" 1 tape in env.
    Offsite Barcode: 31142040619630
  - Legacy of a Mother's Murder (In a Child's Name) Box 2, 1989-1991; 31142040619648 (Box 25)
    Notice of tentative writing credits, script drafts, some memo pads, copy of original manuscript of book of the same name by Peter Maas, some handwritten notes and correspondence.
    Offsite Barcode: 31142040619648
  - Legacy of a Mother's Murder (In a Child's Name) Box 2, 31142040619655 (Box 26)
    Notebooks, handwritten notes, plot outlines, scripts and script fragments, copies of legal documents and statutes, interview and conversation transcripts.
    Note: 3-4 inches of research and notes moved to Flat Box 4.
    Offsite Barcode: 31142040619655
  - MK-Ultra Box 1, 1992-1994; 31142040619663 (Box 27)
    Research material. articles, notebooks, interviews, handwritten notes, plot outlines, correspondence.
    "Tape of Haft Conference Call MK/Ultra 9/22/94
    "MK-Ultra notes in limo 9/15/94 and other notes" 1 micro cassette
    "Steven Haft, Dick Russell and me meet in NY re: MK-Ultra 9/20/94" 2 microcassettes in env.
    "MK/Ultra tape Dick Russell and ALK" 1 micro cassette in env.
    "MK/Ultra around the time Dick Russell was here" 1 micro cassette in env.
    Note: Sketch pages moved to Flat Box 5.
    Offsite Barcode: 31142040619663
  - MK-Ultra Box 2, cuid22048 (Box Not Present)
    This group of materials, all found in a file box marked "MK-Ultra miscellaneous notes", have suffered severe water damage at some point and have significant mold growth. They have been tied into a plastic bag and removed for conservation. Materials seem to be preliminary research, articles, magazines, etc. One audio tape.
  - Nine Box 1, 1981-1983; 31142040619671 (Box 28)
    Handwritten and typewritten scripts and script fragments, scene revisions, drafts, notebooks, playbill, 1979 book of musical by Mario Fratti, correspondence, advertising information, auditioning and casting information for out of town companies and national tour, Japanese playbill, show magazine, royalty records, cast album information, news clippings, articles, reviews.
    "Thematic underscoring for opening scene"
    #1 tape of the first parts of the audition"
    "Carla crossover music"
    "'Nine' Inspired by Fellini's 8 1/2"
    Note: 2 folders of contracts and legal pads moved to Flat Box 5.
    Offsite Barcode: 31142040619671
  - Nine Box 2, 1981-1983; 31142040619689 (Box 29)
    Most of this material was taken from labeled folders. Scripts, script fragments, annotations and revisions, writings and input from the cast, head shots, audition notes and material (?), handwritten scene drafts, notebooks, opening night telegrams and correspondence. The bulk of this material is edits and revisions made in preparations and rehearsals for the initial Broadway production.
    "Nine (transcript of film" 1 micro cassette
    "Nine"
    1 empty tape case.
    Offsite Barcode: 31142040619689
  - Phantom Box 1, 1986-91; 31142040619697 (Box 30)
    Phantom was first conceived by Kopit and Maury Yeston as a musical around 1983, then recreated as a non-musical teleplay although the teleplay was aired (in 1990) before the musical premiered (in 1991). Notebooks, handwritten drafts, and typewritten scripts of the teleplay exist here, dated beginning 1988. Also included are correspondence, financial information, chronologies of events, scripts and drafts for the musical, score fragments, reviews, programs, casting notes.
    George Perry, The Complete Phantom of the Opera (Pavilion Books: London, 1987)
    Gaston Leroux, The Phantom of the Opera (Perennial Library: New York, 1987)
    "#2 Phantom" 1 micro cassette
    Offsite Barcode: 31142040619697
  - Phantom Box 2, 1986-1996; 31142040619135 (Box 31)
    Index cards, handwritten drafts and revisions, typescripts, notebooks, correspondence, articles, image research on the Paris Opera House; large quantity of information on regional productions of the musical including programs, reviews, casting, magazines; reviews and press for teleplay; detailed financial records of Phantom production of Theater Under the Stars, Houston; photos; cast album material; royalty agreements.
    Note: Some photos in folder marked photos.
    Note: 4 folders of sketch pages and pad, notes, magazine and photo research moved to Flat Box 5.
    Offsite Barcode: 31142040619135
  - Phantom Box 3, 1989-1996; 31142040619143 (Box 32)
    Materials on local productions, interviews, news clippings, teleplay script and revisions, notebook, correspondence, teleplay shooting schedules and other records of time in Paris, production schedules.
    Offsite Barcode: 31142040619143
  - Roy Steinberg Project, 1997; 31142040619150 (Box 33)
    Small amount of material for an apparently undeveloped project at that time titled "Carry and Dump"; handwritten notes, character summaries, script for episode of daytime soap opera "Guiding Light" (Roy Steinberg was a producer)
    "Norma in Wonderland" 1 micro cassette in env.
    Note: Small amount of materials, will fit into Ms. box. Small amount of oversized sketchbook pages moved to Flat Box 6.
    Offsite Barcode: 31142040619150
  - The Road to Nirvana Box 1, 1989-1995; 31142040619168 (Box 34)
    Records of publication, reviews, materials on various regional productions (correspondence, rights and royalty material, script amendments, auditions, etc.), receipts and expenses, correspondence, programs; early copies of script.
    "Nirvana--Who Am I" in padded env.
    Note: Roll of posters from Steppenwolf production, handbills, three legal folders of galleys moved to Flat Box 6.
    Offsite Barcode: 31142040619168
  - The Road to Nirvana Box 1a, 1988-1995; 31142040619184 (Box 35)
    Early copies and drafts of the script. Many of these drafts use the working title of the play: "Bone-the-Fish"
    Offsite Barcode: 31142040619184
  - Roswell Box 1, 1992-1994; 31142040619176 (Box 36)
    Research materials, including books, video tapes, news clippings and articles, issues of the "Skeptical Inquirer", notebooks, correspondence, galley copy of "UFO Crash at Roswell", screenplays and revisions.
    John A. Keel, Operation Trojan Horse (Abacus: London, 1973)
    Kevin D. Randle and Donald R. Schmitt, UFO Crash at Roswell (Avon Books: New York, 1991)
    "Ron Reagan Show on UFOs" VHS